Guide to the Tangren Alexander papers Coll 746
University of Oregon Libraries, Special Collections and University Archives
- Work by others, 1916-2021, undated; 7.
  - Southern Oregon Women Writers' Group, 1983-2021, undated; 7.1.
    - "Fran's version of me", 1999 (Box 9, Folder 68)
    - "Hannah's Readings", 2005 (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - Woman of Power, magazine, 1992 Summer (Box 9, Folder 70)
    - "A Woman's Voice," songsheet, "sung at WG Portland Reading", 1988 (Box 9, Folder 71)
    - "Writers' Group", 2019-2021 (Box 9, Folder 72)
    - "Writers' Group bookplate", undated (Box 9, Folder 73)
    - "Writers Group Fall Gathering 9-7-03," VHS tapes, 2003 September 7 (Box 20, Cassette 1-2)
    - Writers' Group in Portland, mockup, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 74)
    - "Writers' Group Reading at the Last Fall WomanSource Gathering", 2003 (Box 9, Folder 75)
    - "Writers' Group website", 2012 (Box 9, Folder 76)
    - "Writers' Group writings", 2002-2003 (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - Tee Corinne material, circa 1968-2008, undated; 7.2.
    - "Community Herstories graphics", 1984-1991 (Box 9, Folder 78)
    - "Community Herstories: Living in Southern Oregon, work done in early 1990s", 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 79-80)
    - "Gryphon: Another Colored Drag Queen by Tee A. Corinne," VHS tape, 1991 January 22 (Box 20, Cassette 3)
    - "Lesbian Photography on the U.S. West Coast 1972-1997," printout, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 81)
    - "The Little Houses on Women's Land," emails, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 82)
    - Lovers: Love and Sex Stories, undated (Box 9, Folder 83)
    - Lovers, manuscript, undated (Box 9, Folder 84)
    - Miscellaneous works by Corinne, 1985, undated (Box 9, Folder 85)
    - "Miscellaneous writings", circa 1968-1995 (Box 10, Folder 1-3)
    - "On Our Backs, interview with Tee", 2002 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Portrait photograph, undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Publicity material, 1998-2008 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - "The Sex Lives of Daffodils: An Autobiography, old version," manuscript, 5.25-inch floppy disk, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - "Tangren Reading the afterword to book 3," drawings, 1983-1985 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Tee Corinne: Twenty-Two Years 1970-1992, circa 1992 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - "Tee's drawings, writers' group early '80s and other art by Tee Corinne", circa 1981-1983 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Variations on a Queerly Appealing Theme, manuscript, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - "What is revealed: Lesbian art books come of age," in Circles magazine, 1997 January / February (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - "Writings about Tee's death", 2006 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - "Yantras of Womanlove reductions", undated (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Collected writings and clippings, 1916-2020, undated; 7.3.
    - "Ann Southcombe", 2012 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - "Bethroot's poetry, Nancy (solipcism)," "Madrone 70th birthday", 1999, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Blue Heron, Hannah, "From the Other Side of Madness", circa 1980s (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Booklets, 1987-2004 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Boyle, Chloe Rose, "A Fairy In My Pocket", undated (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - "Brigid's Song," "Brigid's Dance", undated (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Budapest, Z., Selene: The Most Famous Bull-Leaper On Earth, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Byron, Marion Anne Penning, Just Tell It Like It Is, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Carol, Chris, Amazon Baby: Songs for Women, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Carol, Chris Silver Wheel, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - "Carole Gale writing, photographs", 2005 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Castelou, Carol, "Elizabeth the Dog", undated (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Collected writings, 1965-1989 (Box 10, Folder 25-26)
    - Commons, Giselle, Christine Butterfield, Passion is a Forrest Fire Between Us, 1983, undated (Box 10, Folder 27-28)
    - Crone Chronicles: A Journal of Conscious Aging, 1999 Summer (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - "Deborah Kerr magazines", 1956-1959 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Deborah Kerr material, photocopies, undated (Box 10, Folder 31)
    - "Fairy Tale for a Queen", undated (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - "Feminist Periodicals: A current listing of contents", 1981 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - The Feminist Writers Guild National Newsletter, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - "Friends' writings", circa 1997-2020 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - "From Journal, September 26, 2000"`, 1998-2001 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Gale, Carole, 2000-2011 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - "The Garden According to Eve," artwork, circa 2001 (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - "Gay Marriage articles", 2004 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - Goddess Rising, No. 2, Autumn Equinox, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Gwynn, Bethroot, "Debriefing from a Goddess of Mesopotamia During War on Iraq", 2003 April (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - Hopp, Julie, "Julie's poetry book", undated (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - "In journal", 1986-2006 (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - "Interesting articles", 1956-1989 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - "Interesting graphics", circa 1979 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - "Interesting science articles", 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - Kerr, Deborah, The Men in My Arms, undated (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - Laurence, Helen, 2000-2004 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - "Lesbian Archives newsletters", 1981-2004 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - The Lesbian Review of Books, vol. VI, No. 1, 1999 Fall (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - "The Man I Married," Silver Screen magazine, 1948 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - "Midwives of Winter: an anthology in the making by Sandra Pastorius", 1989 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - "Midwives of Winter," 3.5-inch floppy disk, 1989 November 21 (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - Northwest Women's Report, NWWSA, 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - "Oregon Women's Land Trust handbook", circa 1990s (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Overman, Caroline, If This Be Madness: The Journal of a Psychiatric Patient, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Parabola, 1977 Summer (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Paré, Louise, She Brings All Things Forth From Her Body, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Perkins Gilman, Charlotte, "With Her in Ourland, The Forerunner", 1916 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - "Philosophical Approach and Theoretical Orientation," "Gwen's Orals", after 1993 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Piercy, Marge, "Why Marry at All?", undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - "Poor Women in Timber Country, Bev Brown", 1991 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - The Radical, Discourse and Disclosure, newspapers, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Ransom, Donald, poetry, undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - "Review of UnInvited", 2005 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - "Ruth Mountain's song about Tangren Alexander", circa 1980-1985 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - "Sample copies of review publications", 1984 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - "Sandra Pastorius", 1970s-1980s (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Smith, Izetta, "The Death of a Mother Through the Eyes of a Daughter", circa 1990 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Society for Women in Philosophy, Pacific Division, newsletter, 1989 Spring (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - "Song of the Wild", 1985 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Tax, Meredith, "In the Year of Harry Potter, Enter the Dragon", 2002 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Taylor, Donna, undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - WomanSource Rising News, 2008-2010 (Box 11, Folder 18-19)
    - WomanSource Rising News, Oregon Women's Land Trust Newsletter, 2004-2011 (Box 11, Folder 20-21)
    - WomanSpirit, 1979 Summer (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - The Women Press, 1982-1987 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Women's press, newspaper, 1980 June/July (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - "Writing by Friends, Libré, Thyme", 1992 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - "Xeroxed articles", circa 1981 (Box 11, Folder 26)